Lalit Kakkar

Full Stack Developer

Agra, India · +91-8433408211 · lalitkakkar50@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/lalit-kakkar50

Competent Web Developer with years of experience working with tech startups and freelance. Creative and people-oriented. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP, React JS, JavaScript, CSS, and MySQL.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digikolorz, Agra, India

July 2023 - current

Frontend Developer

- Built responsive websites for clients using HTML5, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and CSS compiled using Maven and Webpack build tools.
- Implemented functionality and interactivity using JavaScript, enhancing user engagement and experience.

Anand's Valley, New Delhi, India

May 2022 - July 2023

Web Developer Intern

- Responsible for creating UI & admin panel functionality like (add, delete & edit) products for client's e-commerce website.
- Provided ongoing website maintenance and support, addressing client requests and implementing updates as needed.

PERSONAL PROJECT

Airline Reservation System(aeroscape.infinityfreeapp.com)

- Airline Reservation System(Aeroscape) is a platform designed to meet the demand of clients booking a particular flight online to a certain destination.
- Frontend of the website is built using HTML, CSS(Bootstrap) & and the Javascript backend is built using PHP, and the database uses SQL.

EDUCATION

Lovely Professional University, Phagwara, Punjab

2020-2023

Bachelor of Technology - Computer Science & Engineering

Grade: 7.29 out of 10

Lovely Professional University, Phagwara, Punjab

2017-2020

Diploma — Computer Science & Engineering

Grade: 7.04 out of 10

St. George's College, Agra, India

2017

Xth - Science **Grade: 58%**

SKILLS

Frontend:- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Javascript, ReactJS. **Backend:-** Node js, express js, PHP, SQL, WordPress, REST API.

Languages: Hindi(Native), English(Fluent)